TOMAS JONG



KS 67337, United States



bru.jon0129@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a front end engineer with 10 years of experience.

So far I participated in more than 30+ projects successfully and I have rich experience in vast area. Development is my life and I used to satisfy all the requirements coming from the clients and users. As a problem solver, I like to challenge coding and I have a good team spirit.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Jul. 2019 – Feb. 2022 Singapore

Senior Frontend Engineer, Enjin.io

Enjin offers a suite of integrated products that make non-fungible tokens (NFTs) easy for individuals, businesses, and developers.

I was responsible for developing the frontend part mainly.

- Figma to HTML/CSS
- · Worked with Javascript frameworks and libraries
- · Worked with blockchain developers

Mar. 2016 - May. 2019 United States

Senior Frontend Developer, Fortnite

Fortnite is a free-to-play Battle Royale game with numerous game modes for every type of game player. Watch a concert, build an island or fight.

I was responsible for developing the frontend parts.

- Sketch to React
- API Integration
- Code Optimization, Unit Test

Jun. 2013 - Mar. 2016 United States

Full Stack Engineer, Red Apple Interactive Pharmacy

Red Apple Interactive Pharmacy is a next generation retail pharmacy with a goal of advancing and broadening the delivery of retail health in an interactive way.

I worked as a full stack engineer.

- Website Development with custom PHP framework and vanilla Javascript
- App Development with Ionic
- jQuery Mobile Development

EDUCATION

Mar. 2013

Bachelor of Science: Computer Science

• University of Kalmar - Kalmar

SKILLS

Expert • React/Next

Expert • Vue/Nuxt

Expert • Angular

Expert • Node.js

Expert	•	Javascript/Typescript
Expert	•	Web3/Solidity
Expert	•	React Native
Expert	•	PHP & PHP Frameworks
Expert	•	MySQL, MongoDB, Firebase, etc
Expert	•	Git
Experienced	•	Django/Python
Experienced	•	Dev Ops
Experienced	•	Third API Integration (Paypal, Stripe, Twilio, GraphQL, etc)